(Leonard:)Hey, guys,
what do you think?
(Leonard:)Priya took me
clothes shopping.
(Penny:)Hey, you look great.
(Penny:)Good for you, Priya.
(Penny:)I could never get that stupid
hoodie off him
(Penny:)when we were...
(Penny:)Well, you look great.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Priya:)Lets go hang
everything up.
(Leonard:)Yeah, good.
(Leonard:)New contacts.
(Leonard:)I should have done this
years ago.
(Howard:)So you finally getting used to
them doing it on a daily basis?
(Penny:)I'm not going out with him.
(Penny:)He can sleep
with whoever he wants.
(Howard:)Yeah, I was talking to Raj.
(Penny:)Oopsy.
(Sheldon:)This deck is rigged in
some fashion.
(Howard:)Fine. Get another deck
(Howard:)and I'll do
the trick with that.
(Sheldon:)So you're saying this is
a regulation deck?
(Howard:)I'm saying believe in magic,
you muggle.
(Penny:)You know, well, I'm happy
Leonard's found someone.
(Penny:)Not that anybody asked.